jangosmtp.com 2010-12-31

# SMTP Relay - JangoSMTP Privacy Statement

JangoSMTP has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm and continuing commitment to the privacy of personal information provided by those visiting and interacting with the JangoSMTP public web site and the JangoSMTP application (for clients). We hold the privacy of your personal information in the highest regard. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website. 

### Your Email Lists and Databases

JangoSMTP and its parent company JangoMail, Inc. will never sell, rent, share, or otherwise make available your email lists and/or databases to anyone except internal support personnel who may be assisting you in troubleshooting your account, unless it is required to do so in connection with legal process or in accordance with any law, regulation or order of a court or regulatory agency of competent jurisdiction. JangoSMTP is not in the business of selling data. JangoSMTP is in the business of providing a robust SMTP service. 

### The Information We Collect

Our registration forms require users to give us contact information that may include name, email address, address, and facts about your company size, and similar information. We only require a credit card from users if they are signing up for paid services. We never sell, share or trade any of our customer information with other companies. 

### Security Technology

JangoSMTP has made a substantial investment in the latest server, database, backup and firewall technologies to protect our information assets. These technologies are deployed as part of sophisticated security architecture. All data resides in a tightly controlled, secure data center. These investments mean that information about the identity and preferences of individual members is never accessible to anyone outside JangoSMTP. We will maintain safeguards to protect the security of these servers and your personally identifiable information. 

### Acquisition or Changes in Ownership of JangoSMTP

In the event that JangoSMTP (or a substantial portion of its assets) is acquired, customer information would be considered part of those assets, and may be part of those assets that are transferred. 

### Policy Modifications

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If/when JangoSMTP makes changes to this privacy statement, we will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically. 

### Contacting JangoSMTP about Privacy

If you have any questions about our privacy statement, the information we have collected from you online, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact: 

JangoSMTP Inquiries  
JangoSMTP  
P.O. Box 751024  
Dayton, OH 45475  
Or see the Contact Us page
